https://greatlakesscrapbookevents.com/show-policies/

Home / Privacy and Security
Registration Confirmation: Online registrants will receive instant confirmation after processing their registration.  Mailed in registration forms received before the postmark deadline will be emailed confirmation if an email address is provided.  If no email address is provided, confirmation will be mailed.  Please be sure to provide us with accurate e-mail and mailing addresses. You will pick up your registration materials when you arrive at theConvention Center – THESE ITEMS WILL NOT BE MAILED TO YOU IN ADVANCE OF THE CONVENTION!  With proper written authorization from the person named on the tickets, you may pick up another person’s registration packet in the event that they are unable to attend.
Privacy Policy:  Our Pledge to You, Our Customer
Scrapbooks Mega Meet, LLC dba Great Lakes Scrapbook Events (GLSE) respects your privacy. We do not sell, rent, loan or transfer any personal information regarding our customers to any unrelated third parties, with the exception of basic mailing information which is made available to duly registered exhibitors and sponsors at our event if requested. Any information you give us about yourself is held with the utmost care and security and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented.
Information collected on our Web site is collected and used by Great Lakes Scrapbook Events and its subsidiaries and affiliates (“Great Lakes Mega Meet”, “Birch Run Scrapbooking & Stamping Show”, “Arctic Blast Crop”, and other events produced by GLSE) and, in limited cases, GLSE service providers who are subject to confidentiality agreements. Basic mailing information is made available to duly registered exhibitors at our event if requested.  GLSE  will not collect any personal information about customers except when specifically and knowingly provided by them.
Use of Information
Information collected by GLSE is used by us for two main purposes. First, we collect information to figure out how to improve our site by seeing which areas, features and products are most popular. Second,  we collect information to enable customers  to conduct transactions on our Web site.  If we want to collect information for other purposes, we will inform you when we collect the information.
From time to time, we may use a limited number of service providers to assist us with customer service, such as answering telephone calls and e-mails. These service providers only use customer information to assist our customers. They must keep all customer information strictly confidential and return it to GLSE when our agreements with them end. Thus, the information collected by these service providers is controlled by GLSE and will only be used for the purposes described in this policy.
On occasion, GLSE may also share non-personal, summary information regarding our customers with unrelated third parties (for example, we publicly disclose the aggregate number of registered users of our Web site). However, GLSE does not share any personal information about any particular customer with unrelated third parties, with the exception of duly registered event exhibitors who have requested mailing information.
Security
At Great Lakes Scrapbook Events, part of our job is to make sure your registration experience is safe and secure. That means your credit card is safe, your personal information is safe, and your password is safe. We use the latest encryption technologies, rigorous password protections, and stringent limits on the number of people who have access to your information, all to guard against unauthorized access to the data.  We do not retain your credit card information on our servers once your transaction has been processed.
Questions and Comments
If you have additional questions or comments of any kind, or if you see anything on our web site that you think is inappropriate, please let us know or e-mail us at:
Scrapbooks Mega Meet, LLC dba Great Lakes Scrapbook Events – Online Safety & Privacy
PO Box 71226
Madison Heights, MI 48071
Comments are closed, but trackbacks and pingbacks are open.
Follow Us0likes210followers161followersRecent Posts
VOLUME – November 2020 – Pre Black Friday – Show SpecialsOn: Nov 18, 2020No Comments
VOLUME – November 2020 – Pre Black Friday – Event SponsorsOn: Nov 12, 2020No Comments
VOLUME – November 2020 – Pre-Black Friday – Event ScheduleOn: Nov 05, 2020No Comments
Blog CategoriesBlog Categories
Select Category
2011 GLMini  (8)
2012 Class Previews  (19)
2012 GLMM  (19)
2013 Class Previews  (36)
2013 GLMM  (39)
2014 Class Preview  (23)
2014 GLMM  (27)
2015 GLMM  (28)
2015 GLMM Class Previews  (23)
2016 GLMM  (2)
2016 GLMM Class Previews  (21)
2017 GLMM  (30)
2017 GLMM Class Previews  (25)
2018 GLMM  (29)
2018 GLMM Class Previews  (28)
2019 GLMM  (26)
2019 GLMM Class Previews  (25)
2020 Columbus  (9)
2020 Columbus Class Previews  (6)
2020 GLMM  (21)
2020 GLMM Classes  (20)
2020 VOLUME  (26)
General Scrapbooking  (2)
News  (52)
Press Releases  (1)
Great Lakes Scrapbook EventsPO Box 621Hartland, MI, 48353Phone: (248) 583-7133More InformationMedia
Privacy and Security
Photo Galleries
Contact Us
Make a Payment
Making a payment for (For use by Vendors and Retreat Guests ONLY):
Sign Up for Our Newsletter Subscribe Now!
© 2020 Great Lakes Scrapbook Events
Go Top
UA-136887306-1
